We intercepted a transmission
on Balnab.
- Bunch of talk of a secret network.
I need to find out where they are, Leia.
Too many people are looking for you.
You put us all in danger.
I need your help.
She's ten years old.
I won't leave her there.
Let go! Let me out!
It's suicide.
I'll go with him.
I have officer clearance.
I can get you inside,
and I can get you access.
Here we go.
A traitor!
A child and an old man.
Was it worth it?
Betraying everything you are.
This was never who I was.
Come on. Get in.
All right, I'm right behind you.
Wade!
You're certain the tracker is with him?
Yes, my Lord.
Where he goes,
it will follow.
Ah, there you are.
Was beginning to think
you weren't coming, Master.
Good.
Then, maybe I stand
more of a chance this time.
Are you ready?
Are you?
Then, let's begin.
My Lord.
The Third Sister is here.
It is my great honor
to be invited aboard, Lord Vader.
I am not interested in civilities.
Where is he?
The tracker worked.
He's arriving on Jabiim as we speak.
You have done well.
Kneel...
Grand Inquisitor.
Set a course, Captain.
We leave for Jabiim at once.
We got her.
Haja?
What are you doing here?
I had nowhere else to go.
Right after I saw you, I got into a fight
with that scary lady Inquisitor.
Now, I'm wanted by the Empire.
But now, I know what it feels like
being a real Jedi.
It's not easy.
This place is a good
business opportunity though.
On you go.
Roken,
that transport,
I need to get her back to Alderaan.
Once we get all these people out of here,
I'll do whatever you want.
They've been waiting for months.
We used an old trade route to get them out
but the window's closing.
We held it to help you get the kid.
We only have a few hours.
It's going to be all right.
The Path will protect us.
We'll do whatever we can to help.
All right, all right, let's hurry it up.
Get ready for dust-off.
Leave anything you don't need.
My Lord, we're approaching Jabiim.
Lock down the facility.
If we seal them in now,
they can hold out for days.
If we cannot break them...
It is not them we need to break.
"The light will fade,
but is never forgotten."
- What's happening?
- The controls aren't responding.
An Imperial Destroyer
just arrived in orbit above us.
She must have tracked us.
It's not her. It's Vader.
He wants us to surrender.
If we surrender, he'll kill us all.
He'll attack next.
He hasn't the patience for a siege.
How do you know?
You grow too aggressive, Anakin.
Be mindful.
A Jedi's goal is to defend life,
not take it.
Mercy doesn't defeat an enemy, Master.
Which is why you're gonna lose.
Launch the attack.
There, there. It'll be okay.
Everyone.
I understand you're scared.
The Empire will attack soon.
They're stronger than us,
better equipped, better trained.
If we try and fight them,
we will not survive.
But we do not need to fight them.
We just need to hold them off long enough
to get you all out.
Roken, how much time do you need
to override the doors?
Three, four hours.
You have one.
And block every other remote access.
Everyone else, we're gonna lock down
every other entrance in this facility.
If we defend our position together,
then by the time they get inside,
we'll be gone.
You heard him.
Let's move it, people! Let's go!
Seal all the doors.
Move. Move! Move! Move now!
Steady fire! Steady fire!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Man positions!
Attack!
Lock it in.
Full load, full power.
Fire!
Light 'em up!
It's a heavy gun.
They're trying to blast
through the outside door.
Roken, we need the hangar roof open.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
That was underwhelming.
I don't need your opinion.
Did you try going in the vents
to see what's going on?
I'm a little too big
to be crawling around in the vents.
Would you like to try?
I'm going to need a ladder.
It's not playtime right now, Princess.
Do as she asks.
You trust me? I trust her.
Get her the ladder.
Get her a ladder. Quick.
Right away!
Leia.
Be careful.
Haja, will you keep your eye on her?
- I am not a babysitter, Ben.
I have to go.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I know we said no communication,
but your silence worries me.
If he's found you,
if he's learned of the children...
If I don't hear from you soon,
I'll head to Tatooine.
Owen will need help with the boy.
I pray you're safe, Obi-Wan.
Both of you.
Is everything all right?
It will be.
You know, I was following orders on Garel.
The Empire said it was a roundup.
People not paying their way,
taxes for the cause.
They lied.
There were four families,
all Force-sensitive,
and we,
we gathered them up.
I didn't know who they were. I didn't know
what the Inquisitors would do.
Fourteen people died,
and six of them were children,
and I couldn't do anything to help them.
So now, I do this.
One for every one I get through.
You're right, Ben.
Some things you can't forget.
But you can fight to make them better.
We're in trouble.
Here. Got enough rounds?
I don't know how long it's gonna hold.
We got a plan B here?
We're going to have to slow them down.
Tell the Inquisitor I want to talk.
She started this when she kidnapped Leia.
I'll buy as much time as I can.
He's requesting to negotiate.
If this is you stalling for time,
it won't work.
Lord Vader will have you at any cost.
You mean, Anakin.
You knew who Vader was.
Back on Daiyu, how did you know that?
Vader would have kept that hidden,
and you're too young to have known him.
Unless...
Unless you were there.
It doesn't matter where I was.
The night of Order 66,
you were a youngling.
That's how you knew. You saw him.
Stop.
- Anakin killed the others.
- That's enough.
He killed the other younglings,
- but somehow you su--
- Enough. Enough!
We thought he was there to help us.
I tried to help them, but I couldn't.
I was too weak.
When he left,
I played dead.
Hid with the bodies.
Felt them go cold.
They were the only family I knew,
and he slaughtered them.
You're not serving him, are you?
You're hunting him.
Let me help you.
Why would I ever trust you?
- Because we want the same thing.
- Do we, Obi-Wan?
Do you really want Anakin dead?
Where were you
while he was killing my friends?
He was your Padawan.
Why didn't you stop him?
Why didn't you save us?
I don't need your help.
I don't need anyone.
You won't stop him alone.
You have no idea what I've done alone.
Fall back to second position!
Let's go!
Don't let them pass!
All squads, forward!
Into the breach!
Fire!
Over there! Over there!
Hold your ground!
Don't let them through!
Squad Eight, advance!
Take cover!
Flank left!
Take them down!
Go! Go!
Go!
Retreat! Everyone, get back!
Run for your lives!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! I've got you!
After them!
Leia, we got to hurry.
Are you listening to me?
I feel like you're not listening to me.
Would you stop talking?
He said it was a red breaker. Red.
I know what he said.
Go! Go! Go! Retreat!
Go! Move!
- Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Move!
- I've got you. Come on.
No mercy! Seal them in!
- Block the tunnel!
- No!
Quick!
- Tala!
- No!
Wipe them out!
Tala!
No! Tala!
Go!
No!
May the Force be with you.
Get back!
Please tell me we're close.
Leia, you close?
Working on it.
She's working on it.
The Grand Inquisitor
has breached the walls.
We shall have him soon.
Tell her to stand down.
My Lord?
Kenobi is already ours.
There's no way out, Master.
Admit you are beaten.
What is it?
What's wrong?
It's over.
I'm going back.
You can't quit.
I fought for too long.
You can't just throw that away.
It won't make a difference.
They want all of us.
- Vader wants me.
- If you surrender, she died for nothing.
- He'll keep coming.
- That's why I have to stop him.
You're going to fight him?
He expects me to surrender.
He knows I'll do everything I can
to protect these people.
You'll be on your own.
No.
Haja, look out for her, will you?
You want to tell me
how you're gonna fight without a weapon?
There are other ways to fight.
Seize him.
Come on, where is it?
Inform Lord Vader,
Kenobi is ours.
He's on his way.
You're gonna die soon.
You're not bringing him to me.
I'm bringing him to you.
This isn't over yet.
There are families back there.
Children.
Are you gonna let him do it again,
what he did to you?
We could end this together.
What makes you think
he won't see it coming?
Because all he'll see is me.
There.
Your weapon's gone.
It's over.
Your need for victory, Anakin,
it blinds you.
Where is he?
I have him secured inside, my Lord.
I will bring him in myself.
Come on. Come on.
There it is.
- Lola? What are you doing in here?
Lola, stop! Stop!
A restraining bolt?
- Got it.
Much better.
Got it.
Okay.
All right, everybody, run!
Come on, let's go.
Everything's all set.
Leia!
Well done!
Where's Tala?
Help who you can.
Let's go!
Let's get to the transport, people!
Move! Move! Let's go!
Come on. We need to get to the transport.
You're a great warrior, Anakin,
but your need to prove yourself
is your undoing.
Until you overcome it,
a Padawan you will still be.
He was wise to use you against me.
Did you really believe
I did not see it, youngling?
You are of no further use.
Hello, Third Sister.
Revenge does wonders for the will
to live, don't you think?
Your rage
was useful.
Now it is tiresome.
We will leave you where we found you.
In the gutter, where you belong.
Goodbye...
Grand Inquisitor.
Our hyperdrive is down,
and they're behind us.
Kenobi,
are you listening to me?
Something's wrong.
If he's found you,
if he's learned of the children...
I'll head to Tatooine.
Owen wi--
Help the boy.
What is it?
Are you okay?
I'm sure it's nothing.
Thank you, Roken.